KOOTHRAPPALI:
I wonder
(Raj:)if he's listening
to our music right now.
(Howard:)Could you imagine?
(Howard:)What a cool way
for us to meet.
(Howard:)He's playing our song and
looks up, and there we are...
(Howard:)his favorite two-piece acoustic
sci-fi novelty rock band.
(Raj:)And he's, all, like,
"Aren't you the guys from
Footprints on the Moo...?"
(Raj:)Ooh, what is he doing?!
(Howard:)I can't watch.
I-I-It's okay.
(Raj:)Oh, it's okay.
He's done.
Why is he looking at it?!
(Raj:)Eh, no, he's not going
to eat it, is he?
(Howard:)Come on, Trent,
you're better than...
(both groaning)
(Howard:)Let's just go.
(Trent:)Hey, aren't you
the guys...?
Nope!
Never heard of 'em!
♪ ...Know if words could say ♪
♪ But darlin',
I'll find a way... ♪
(Sheldon:)I wonder why it was
this particular song
(Sheldon:)that was stuck
in my head.